Sarah Pettigrew

123 South Street, New York, NY 12345 sarah.p@youremail.com (987) 654-3210

Highly motivated bookkeeper with over eight years of experience in handling and documenting financial transactions. Comprehensive knowledge of bookkeeping procedures and principles. Skilled in producing accurate financial reports within tight deadlines.

Education

Associate of Accounting

New York Training College, New York, NY September 2010 - July 2012

Key Skills

- Customer Service Support
- Organized
- Punctual
- Self-Motivated
- Quickbooks
- Sage
- MS Office
- Team Player
- Data Entry and Analysis
- Problem Solving
- Attention to Detai Is

Certifications

- Certified Payroll Professional, American Payroll 2015
- Quickbooks Expert, 2017

Professional Experience

Bookkeeper

Booker Medical Center, New York, NY | September 2015 - Present

- Document weekly and monthly payrolls
- Assist with Federal, City, and State tax returns
- Process accounts payable and receivable
- Handle patient invoice queries
- Communicate with patients regarding outstanding payments and assist them in developing payments plans
- Input patient details and payment data onto a spreadsheet
- File all paperwork regarding financial transactions
- File medical insurance claims on behalf of patients

Bookkeeper

Goldberg, Miller, and Associates Law Firm, New York, NY | July 2012-August 2015

- Handled payroll for over 100 employees
- Helped to resolve billing disputes and collections
- Maintained all financial records, including bank statements, transactions, and receipts
- Assisted tax preparer with Federal, State, and City tax returns
- Produce monthly financial summaries and reports for senior partners
- Mailed credit memos and statements
- Prepared payroll and direct deposit accounts